What is the biggest misconception that you feel people have about the Black future?
It's a really important question.
But from my point of view, it's that I think it's wrong to be rooted in hopelessness.
I think that when I talk to people like you, when I talk to my peers that I like, I feel like a ton of hope.
I know that things can improve maybe more than we could ever believe.
So I think hopelessness is kind of a mistake.
What's one thing you said in this episode that you would stand 10 toes down on?
A ghost story is a realism story.
It's all real.
It's all true.
When you're writing, there could be monsters and dragons and ghosts, or you could be writing about being in a cubicle or waiting in line at the DMV.
Either way, you have to make it real for the reader.
So it's all realism to me.